A Guide to the University of Virginia Valediction Addresses, 1948-1949, 1969-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Valediction Addresses 1948-1949, 1969-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-30/9/1.062
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These addresses were transferred from the University of Virginia Office of Major Events to the University of Virginia Library on July 14, 1997 and June 1, 1998.
Scope and Content
The collection contains copies of addresses delivered at the University of Virginia between 1948 and 1998. There are speeches delivered by Morris S. Lazaron, 1948; Rev. Peter L. Ireton, 1949; John A. Russell, Jr., 1969; Raymond C. Bice, 1980; Edward M. Kennedy, 1984; Arthur Ashe, 1990; Katie Couric, as printed in the UVA Alumni News, 1992; Tom Brokaw, 1993; Brit Hume, 1994; Marian Wright Edelman, 1995; James Carville, together with excerpts, 1996; Wyatt Andrews, 1997; and, Christopher Reeve, 1998.
With the collection is a list of valedictory speakers, 1971-1998, compiled by the University of Virginia Office of Major Events.
Arrangement
The speeches are arranged in chronological order.
Contents List
- Rabbi Morris S. Lazaron, 1948 (Folder 1)
- Rev. Peter L. Ireton, 1949 (Folder 2)
- John A. Russell, Jr., 1969, 1949 (Folder 3)
- Raymond C. Bice, 1980 (Folder 4)
- Edward M. Kennedy, United States Senator from Massachusetts, 1984 (Folder 4a)
- Arthur Ashe, 1990 (Folder 5)
- Katie Couric, 1992 (Folder 6)
- Tom Brokaw, 1993 (Folder 7)
- Brit Hume, 1994 (Folder 8)
- Marian Wright Edelman, 1995 (Folder 9)
- James Carville, 1996 (Folder 10)
- Wyatt Andrews, 1997 (Folder 11)
- Christopher Reeve, 1998 (Folder 12)